<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on ajannu</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on ajannu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.138.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Crpto Token</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/projects/crypto_token/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/projects/crypto_token/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;creating-a-solana-based-asset-backed-cryptocurrency&#34;&gt;Creating a Solana-Based Asset-Backed Cryptocurrency&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today’s rapidly evolving financial landscape, blockchain technology is transforming how we perceive digital ownership, security, and asset management. My recent project explores these possibilities by creating a unique cryptocurrency token on the Solana blockchain—an asset-backed digital currency designed to bridge traditional value with innovative blockchain technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;//localhost:1313/blog/crypto1.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;
This project began with the creation and deployment of a custom Solana token. Using Solana’s robust programming model and consensus mechanisms, I developed a scalable cryptocurrency designed for speed, security, and efficiency. To add intrinsic value to this token, I integrated asset-backed functionality. This feature enables the token to represent and hold real-world or digital assets, turning it into a viable store of value and unique asset holder.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local AI Server</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/projects/local_ai_server/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/projects/local_ai_server/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this project, I set up a local AI server environment to support efficient AI model deployment and management on a personal machine. Leveraging &lt;strong&gt;Ollama&lt;/strong&gt; for seamless model downloading and &lt;strong&gt;OpenUI&lt;/strong&gt; for intuitive interaction, I created a streamlined platform for working with large language models, like Llama 3, directly on my device. This setup combines the flexibility of Docker for containerized management and Python version control with &lt;strong&gt;pyenv&lt;/strong&gt;, ensuring compatibility across various dependencies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerability Scanner</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/projects/vulnerablity_scanner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/projects/vulnerablity_scanner/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
